## **ABOUT ME**

Creative software developer with 4 years of experience managing IT systems and one year crafting ITSM software at a small consultancy. Desire to use proven technical and communication skills to develop high quality business systems. Enthusiastic to learn new software, surmount engineering hurdles, and hunt down pesky bugs.

# **PROJECT**

#### Job Scraper

Python app that scrapes Indeed for jobs according to input search terms, outputs to a CSV.

# **SKILLS**

#### Languages:

Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL

#### **Operating Systems:**

Linux (Arch/Antergos), MS Windows

#### **DevOps:**

Git

# **IDEs/Text Editors:**

VSCode, nVim

#### Misc:

Relational database schema, Agile methodology

# **ScottGreen**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | Denver, CO

# AWARDS AND PUBLICATIONS

AIRMAN OF THE YEAR - 961st AACS, Kadena AB, 2010

Jackson, E. D.; Green, S. C.; Prieto, A. L. **Electrochemical Performance of Electrodeposited Zn4Sb3Films for Sodium-Ion Secondary Battery Anodes.** ACS Applied Materials & Interfaces 2015, 7 (14), 7447–7450.

## WORK HISTORY

(Sep. 2017 - Sep. 2018)

#### **ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT - T4S Partners**

- Used a declarative scripting language to design multiple back-end systems, including an auto-assignment ticketing system, REST API integration, and email parsing.
- Pair programmed in an end-to-end development pipeline, with Dev., Test and Prod. servers. Coordinated testing, deployment of features, and bug fixes for a SaaS business product.
- Troubleshot production-affecting service outages. Determined causes and implemented solutions, minimizing downtime and improving client relations.

(June 2008 - June 2012)

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN - USAF | Kadena, Japan and Beale, CA

 Operated in teams composed of varied specialties to maintain two AWACS aircraft and a DCGS system.

# **EDUCATION**

(May, 2016)

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, CHEMISTRY** - Colorado State University

- Organized study groups for advanced chemistry courses. Helped improve classmate's grades from C's to A's.
- ACS certified degree with courses in organic, inorganic and physical chemistry, biochemistry, calculus-based statistics and physics.

(Sep. 2016 – August 2017)

MATERIALS SCIENCE ENGINEERING - University of Washington

Advanced coursework in semiconductor theory and design.



